## Mustafa Tunç

## Software Engineer tunc mustafa@icloud.com - +905413661323

I am a software engineer passionate about creating software. I have a strong background in image processing, frontend development and backend development which helps me in my career. I have worked on various projects that have given me a lot of different experiences about mobile, backend and frontend. In my job, I have enjoyed working with teams and sharing knowledge with others. My goal is to keep learning and to use my skills to make good software that people like to use.

## **Work Experience**

### Full Stack Developer - Mobileriz (July 2024 - Present)

- Currently working on an omni channel e-commerce integration project, where I am responsible for designing the UI & UX and developing mobile applications for both iOS and Android, and developing backend to ensure seamless integration and functionality across the platform.
- Used technologies: Python, Flask, FastAPI, SQLAlchemy, Kong, PostgreSQL, Hexagonal Architecture, Apache Kafka, Flink, Docker, Flutter, Riverpod, MVC+S, and Figma.

#### **Mobile Application Developer -** Voco Technology (September 2023 - February 2024)

- Worked on Voco which is a location based social media application that is similar to Tinder and Bumble.
  It allows users to create activities in a specific location where other users can search and participate in that activity.
- I worked on developing mobile applications both for iOS and Android. We created the whole app in 2 months with 2 engineers.
- My main responsibilities were, developing the UI designs, creating profile, sending requests and sharing functionalities within the app. I also created an automated testing solution for the UI.
- Used technologies: Flutter, Riverpod, MVC+S, Google Maps, Push Notification, WebSocket, RestAPI.

#### **Software Engineer -** Ant Arge (February 2022 - September 2023)

- Worked on ANTLY which is a courier delivery application based on a new generation flexible working model. A mobile application where you can earn additional income by accepting order requests from businesses in the region where you want to work. The project is supported by TUBITAK.
  - I created the whole mobile app including its publishing to the App Store, Google Play Store and Huawei App Gallery.
  - Used technologies: Flutter, Provider, MVC, Google Maps, Push Notifications, Firebase, WebSocket.
- Developed CAK, a mobile marketplace app designed to reduce food waste by offering discounted products nearing their best-before date. The project is supported by KOSGEB and TUBITAK.
  - I created the whole mobile app including its publishing to the App Store, Google Play Store and Huawei App Gallery.
  - Used technologies: Flutter, Provider, MVC, Google Maps, Iyzico as Payment Gateway, Push Notifications.

#### Web Developer - Labotecha (September 2020 - April 2021)

- Worked on a project to list and share the deals on different products.
- I developed a form-based website.
- Used technologies: PHP, MySQL,HTML,CSS, JavaScript React,.

#### **Education History**

Bachelor of Science Computer Engineering (English) - Alanya Alaaddin Keykubat University

Year of Graduation: 2023, GPA: 3,41/4.00

• Awarded 4 high honor and 4 honor certificates.

#### **Personal Projects**

#### AI Chat with Video - ZEO Generative AI Hackathon (9-10 September 2023)

- Theme of the hackathon was to use the power of LLMs and build something that was not possible before within 24 hours. We created a project that accepts prompts in a chat format and generates a video response. We generated videos by retrieving the LLM response as a video script, converting it to speech using Text-to-Speech, finding relevant animation and stitching and presenting it as a video.
- We won 3rd place in the hackathon.
- Used technologies: OpenAI ChatGPT API, Remotion, Next.js, React, Google Cloud Text-to-Speech API

## Ki-Eye (September 2022 - June 2023)

- This project helps doctors in the treatment process by calculating the Ki-67 index percentage (the replication rate of cancer cells) through a mobile application. In a study conducted with samples from 100 different patients from the Pathology Department of Alanya Alaaddin Keykubat University Education and Research Hospital, a success rate of approximately 80% was achieved.
- Used technologies: Node.js, PostgreSQL, TypeScript, Python, OpenCV, Flutter, Provider.

### A Smart Home Systems for Hearing Impaired Individuals (May 2022 - October 2022

- This project aids hearing-impaired individuals by notifying them through a mobile app when their doorbell is pressed. It consists of a circuit at the entrance door of the house that will act as a bell and a mobile application. When the bell is pressed, a notification is sent to the application and the hearing impaired individual starts communication with the person at the door. Speech to text and text to speech conversions are made for communication.
- The project received financial support under TUBITAK 2209 A.
- Used technologies: WebSocket, ESP32, Google Cloud Speech-to-Text and Text-to-Speech, Flutter, Firebase.

# Weed Remover (Teknofest Agricultural Unmanned Land Vehicle Competition) (December 2021 - June 2022)

- In the Teknofest Agricultural Unmanned Ground Vehicle Competition, expectation was to create an unmanned ground vehicle that intervenes in weeds on a dirt track with produce and various obstacles such as weeds. The vehicle we have developed is a weeding vehicle that can navigate the track, overcome obstacles, detect and intervene in weeds using image processing techniques.
- I developed image processing and recognition algorithms and control panel web application.
- Used technologies: Python, OpenCV, Keras, WebSocket, JavaScript.

#### **Volunteer Work and Interests**

- Volunteer Young Leader, Ministry of Youth and Sports (Oct 2020 Mar 2023)
- Member, AKFOD (Aksaray Photography Art Association) (Jun 2018 Present)
- Web Officer, 1907 UNIFEB (Oct 2020 Mar 2022)
- Reporter, Social Coding Club (1 year)
- Lecturer, Python and C Programming Language Course
- Organizer, I. Science and Technology Conference